Yeah.
うん
You like dick, right?
チンチン好きでしょ?
I like it.
好きよ
I'm making a face.
顔してるもん
Hey.
ねえ
Try it.
食べてみて
delicious?
美味しい?
Yeah.
うん
Looks delicious.
美味しそうだね
Which crepe is delicious?
さっきのクレープとどっちが美味しい?
Yeah.
うん
Mr. Shu.
シュウさん
Yeah.
うん
Wow, that's amazing.
うわぁ、すごい
Yeah.
うん
That's a cute voice.
可愛い声だね
Yeah.
うん
I couldn't stand it anymore.
我慢できなくなっちゃった
picture?
え?
What?
なによ?
crepe?
クレープ?
No.
いやだ
Chin Chin, where are you?
チンチン、どこ?
I have to say it's cute.
可愛く言わないと
Yeah.
えぇ
Ah, right?
あ、でしょ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
It feels amazing.
すごい気持ちいい
Hey, look.
ちょっと、ほら
Wow, it's wide open.
うわぁ、ぱっかり開いてるよ
Look.
ほら
yeah?
ん?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Look, it's wide open.
ほら、ぱっかり開いてる
Ah, it feels good.
あぁ、気持ちいい
yeah?
ん?
Ah, amazing.
あぁ、すごい
what happened?
どうしたの?
Ah, amazing.
あぁ、すごい
I'm heading out ahead.
先行しながら出てる
Ah, that's amazing.
あぁ、すごいね
It's cute.
可愛いね
Do you want it out?
出してほしいの?
Is it okay inside?
中でいいの?
Ah, then I'll ask you to please come inside.
あぁ、じゃあ中にくださいって言ってもらおう
I'll go.
行くよ
Oh, that's amazing.
おぉ、すごい
That's amazing.
すごいね
of the earth
地球の
...
Junior, let's have a look at Junior.
ジ ュニアはさ、ジュニアいっぱい見てもらおうか、
a little bit.
ちょっと
Would you like to see a lot of juniors?
ジュニアいっぱい見てもらおうか
Hey Junior.
ちょっと、ジュニアを
picture?
え?
Let me expand it a little.
ちょっと、広げてもらおう
picture?
え?
how was it?
どうだった?
Naughty.
えっち
Yeah.
うん
I was already strong.
もう、強かった
Were you strong already?
もう、強かった?
Well then, just a moment.
じゃあ、ちょっと
You're sweating, aren't you?
汗かいちゃったでしょ
Arrange your hair.
髪、整えて
Take a relaxing shower.
ゆっくりシャワー浴びてごらん
hey.
ね
No, wait, what are you doing?
いや、ちょっと、何してんの?
What are you doing?
何してんの?
I did it.
やっちゃった
Because it's over.
終わったから
picture?
え?
Because it's over.
終わったから
Is it finished?
終わったけ?
It's finished.
終わったよ
how was it?
どうだった?
My face is bright red.
顔が真っ赤になってる
what happened?
どうしたの?
what?
何?
I think I'll wash it, too.
洗ってあげようかな、あと
Ah, thank you.
あ、ありがとう
Because she has a nice body.
素敵な体だから
hey.
ね
I think I'll wash it for a while.
洗ってあげようかな、ちょっと
Wow, I'm not wet at all here.
すっごい、全然濡れたなよ、ここ
You look like you have nice hair.
髪がいいって顔してるね
Look this way.
こっち向いて
Wow, a lot came out.
すごい、いっぱい出てきた
I guess it's the one from earlier.
さっきのやつかな
A lot came out.
いっぱい出てきたね
It feels amazing.
すごい気持ちいい
I can only endure it.
我慢できるだけだ